Guide to the Cornwall Miscellanea 1779-2003 MS 011 MS 011 MS 011
Cornwall Historical Society
- Photographic Materials
  - Photographs
    - People
      - W.B. Hubbard, N.D. (Box 24, Folder 30)
        Portrait of W.B. Hubbard
      - Horace Hitchcock, N.D. (Box 24, Folder 31)
        Portrait of Horace Hitchcock.
      - Dr. Hodge, N.D. (Box 24, Folder 32)
        Portrait of Dr. Hodge, who practiced in Cornwall Bridge.
      - Kellogg Family, circa 1900, N.D. (Box 25, Folder 1)
        Photographs of the Kellogg family. Many of the images are of Bessie Kellogg, a teacher who was the daughter of Philo Kellogg and Elizabeth Chipman of East Cornwall. There are also photos of Philo Kellogg and his wife Elizabeth Chipman, and of the Kellogg home.
      - Waller Kilhamson, June 30, 1990 (Box 25, Folder 2)
        Photograph of Waller Kilhamson taking part in a parade with a banner celebrating his "resettlement" of Dudleytown.
      - George Kittle, N.D. (Box 25, Folder 3)
        Photograph of George Kittle.
      - Elizabeth Lansing, N.D. (Box 25, Folder 4)
        Photograph of Elizabeth Lansing.
      - Joseph Lush, Jr., 1975 (Box 25, Folder 5)
        Photograph of fire chief Joseph Lush, Jr. receiving the key to the new fire house from Cornwall First Selectman Kenneth A. Merz.
      - G. Leo Listman, 1899 (Box 25, Folder 6)
        Portrait of G. Leo Listman of West Cornwall.
      - Mallinson Family, 1902, N.D. (Box 25, Folder 7)
        Photographs of Joseph and Maggie Mallinson. Mallinson was the owner of the shear shop on Lower River Road.
      - Marchionna Family, N.D. (Box 25, Folder 8)
        Photographs of Bea and Fred Marchionna.
      - Marsh Family: Part I, 1902-1953, N.D. (Box 25, Folder 9)
        Photographs of the Marsh family. Included are photos of E.W. Marsh and his immediate family, Charles C. Marsh and his daughter Marian Louise Marsh Corban, Mr. and Mrs. Cyrus Marsh, and many images of town librarian Emily E. Marsh.
      - Marsh Family: Part II, 1903-1958, N.D. (Box 25, Folder 10)
        Personal photograph collection of Emily E. Marsh. Marsh grew up on Pine Street and was well known in the community as a librarian, historian, and church organist. Her photos include images of social events featuring friends and family members like Fanny Baldwin, Mrs. McGaw, Elizabeth Wilcox, and Marian Marsh, as well as her family dog, Pearl.
      - Marsh Family: Part III, 1930-1959, N.D. (Box 25, Folder 11)
        Photographs of extended members of the Marsh family collected by Emily E. Marsh. There are photos of Marsh family members from Rockford, Illinois and Lakewood, Ohio, as well as a photo of Catie Marsh of Washington, D.C.
      - Clarence P. Meier, 1966-1982, N.D. (Box 25, Folder 12)
        Photographs of Cornwall postmaster and artist Clarence P. Meier. There are photos of Meier's murals as well as Meier working at a potter's wheel.
      - Oscar Garland McIntire (Box 25, Folder 13)
        Portrait of the Reverend Oscar Garland McIntire.
      - Henry B. Mead, January 1899 (Box 25, Folder 14)
        Portrait of Reverend Henry B. Mead (1839-1903). Mead, a New Hampshire native, was a Congregationalist minister who served Cornwall for a brief period of ttime.
      - Miller Family, 1902, N.D. (Box 25, Folder 15)
        Photographs of the Miller family. The Millers were interrelated to several Cornwall families, such as the Mallinsons and Yutzlers. There are photos of Francis Miller, Freddy Miller, Mary Miller Yutzler, Joseph Charles Miller, Margaret Miller Mallinson, and Louise Miller Mallinson. There is also a family photo taken in Abraham Mallinson's East Haven home showing three generations of the Miller-Mallinson-Yutzler family.
      - Leigh Richmond Miner (Box 25, Folder 16)
        Photograph of Leigh Richmond Miner (1852-1935) and family. Miner was born in Cornwall to George Lewellyn Miner and Eliza Guild and taught at the Hampton Institute in Virginia.
      - James Henry Moser, circa 1974, N.D. (Box 25, Folder 17)
        Photographs of James Henry Moser and his art supplies. A copy of a photo owned by Moser's descendants depicts Moser in his rain gear, and two additional images show his easle and studio sign.
      - G. Nelson, 1889 (Box 25, Folder 18)
        Portrait of Reverend J. Nelson. Nelson was pastor of the Methodist Episcopal Church at Cornwall Center.
      - Leonard J. Nickerson, N.D. (Box 25, Folder 19)
        Portrait of Judge Leonard J. Nickerson.
      - Niles Family, N.D. (Box 25, Folder 20)
        Photograph of Hazel and Mildred Niles in West Cornwall with Alice Horner Russell and Effie Whitney Catelino.
      - Phyllis Wojan, N.D. (Box 25, Folder 21)
        Photograph of Phyllis Wojan.
      - Patrick "Cap" O'Donnell, N.D. (Box 25, Folder 22)
        Photograph of Patrick "Cap" O'Donnell of West Cornwall with Jay Rowe and Lucas Richmond.
      - Oliver Family, 1910-circa 1932, N.D. (Box 25, Folder 23)
        Photographs of the Oliver family of West Cornwall. Many of the photos are of blacksmith William Oliver. There are images of Oliver working at his shop, as well as in formal attire and with his family. There is also a portrait of Ethel Oliver.
      - Oviatt Family, N.D. (Box 25, Folder 24)
        Photographs of the Oviatt family. Many of the photos are of Ed Oviatt, but there are also images of Dell Oviatt, E.W. Oviatt, Will Oviatt, Nellie Oviatt, George Oviatt, and Sybil Oviatt. Additionally, there are photos of Frances B.O. Hubbard, the Oviatt home, and Punch the dog.
      - B.C. Patterson, September 10, 1927 (Box 25, Folder 25)
        Portrait of B.C. Patterson taken on the occasion of his 88th birthday.
      - Payne Family, N.D. (Box 25, Folder 26)
        Photographs of the Payne family. Two of the images are portraits of Sgt. Joseph Benjamin Payne, son of Rufus and Polly Calhoun Payne, who was killed at the Battle of Cold Harbor during the Civil War. The other photo depicts Mike Payne as part of a railroad repair crew with Bill Dinneen, Senior.
      - Perkins Family, October 1939-March 1947 (Box 25, Folder 27)
        Photographs of the Perkins family. One photo shows Clifford Perkins training a pair of steers, and the other shows Mr. and Mrs. Robert Perkins with their family on their 50th wedding anniversary.
      - Ann Peterson, N.D. (Box 25, Folder 28)
        Photograph of Ann Peterson.
      - M.L. Phillips, N.D. (Box 25, Folder 29)
        Portrait of Miss M. L. Phillips.
      - Mrs. F.V.A. Loucks, N.D. (Box 25, Folder 30)
        Portrait of Mrs. F.V.A. Loucks.
      - Lorraine B. Malahan, N.D. (Box 25, Folder 31)
        Photograph of Lorraine B. Malahan.
      - Laura Pickett, N.D. (Box 26, Folder 1)
        Photograph of Laura Pickett.
      - Pierce Family, N.D. (Box 26, Folder 2)
        Portrait of Mr. and Mrs. Hiram Pierce.
      - Larry Pool, 1986, N.D. (Box 26, Folder 3)
        Photographs of Larry Pool at a formal dinner.
      - Pratt Family, circa 1900, N.D. (Box 26, Folder 4)
        Photographs of the Pratt family. One photo is a portrait of West Cornwall businessman Russell R. Pratt, and the other shows the Pratt family taking a wagon to church.
      - Prentice Family, circa 1950-1989, N.D. (Box 26, Folder 5)
        Prentice family photographs. There is a collection of photos taken of artwork by the Prentice family, as well as a photo of the Tim and Marie Prentice House. Additionally, there is a picture of Maureen Cole Prentice at the Cornwall Observation Post.
      - Read Family, N.D. (Box 26, Folder 6)
        Photographs of Alison Read and Jean Read.
      - Reeds Family, N.D. (Box 26, Folder 7)
        Photographs of a Reeds family dinner.
      - Esther G. Rogers, N.D. (Box 26, Folder 8)
        Photographs of Esther G. Rogers. The collection includes photos of Rogers as an infant, through childhood, and into adulthood. One image depicts four generations of Rogers' family, including Artemesia Wheaton, Mrs. James A. Cochrane, Jessie C. Rogers, and Esther.
      - James Rogers, N.D. (Box 26, Folder 9)
        Photographs of James Cochrane Rogers. Photos include images of Rogers as a child through adulthood. Many of the pictures show Rogers working on his farm or with his family.
      - Jessie Cochrane Rogers, 1902, N.D. (Box 26, Folder 10)
        Photographs of Jessie Cochrane Rogers. Photos include portraits and an image of Jessie with her husband Miner P. Rogers.
      - Rogers Family, 1902, N.D. (Box 26, Box 11)
        General photographs of the Rogers family and their farm. There are photos of Colonel Anson Rogers, Principal Ambrose S. Rogers, Justice Edward Rogers, Daniel L. Rogers, Julia Emeline Corban Rogers, Nellie L. Rogers, Harriet F. Rogers, Louise, Charles, and Estelle Rogers, Olive Rogers, Charlie Rogers, and Edward Rogers.
      - Saleski-Crosby Family, N.D. (Box 26, Folder 12)
        Photographs of the Saleski-Crosby family of West Cornwall.
      - Sandmeyer Family (Box 26, Folder 13)
        Photograph of Kate, Harriet, and Martha Sandmeyer posing with a dog.
      - Mary Schefflien, N.D. (Box 26, Folder 14)
        Photographs of Mary Schefflien practicing music with a group of students, including Jan Walker.
      - Louis H. Schutte, N.D. (Box 26, Folder 15)
        Portrait of Louis H. Schutte. Schutte was the headmaster of the Rumsey Hall School and lived in Cornwall for nearly fifty years before his death in April 1957.
      - Vincenzo Rondinone, circa 1925-circa 1935, N.D. (Box 26, Folder 16)
        Photographs of Vincenzo Rondinone. Rondinone was a skilled potter and worked at the pottery on the Castle property owned by Dr. and Mrs. Martin. Many of the photos show Rondinone at work in the pottery, and one depicts him with his son Nicholas and a team of oxen. The images in this collection were donated by Nicholas Rondinone.
      - Sandford Family (Box 26, Folder 17)
        Photographs of the Sandford family. Photos include images of Helen Sandford Tankersly, L. Sandford, and Mrs. T. R. Sandford, as well as Evelyn Smith.
      - Lewis Sawyer, N.D. (Box 26, Folder 18)
        Portrait of Lewis Sawyer.
      - Scoville Family, 1898-1920, N.D. (Box 26, Folder 19)
        Photographs of the Scoville family and their farm. Photos include images of Jacob Scoville and Samuel Scoville and scenes of various work being done on the farm, such as snow plowing and sap collecting.
      - Helen E. Sedgwick, N.D. (Box 26, Folder 20)
        Portrait of Helen E. Sedgwick.
      - Shepard Family, N.D. (Box 26, Folder 21)
        Portraits of Representative Elbert Shepard and Representative Eliphalet H. Shepard.
      - Smith Family, N.D. (Box 26, Folder 22)
        Photographs of the Smith family. One photo depicts George and David Smith on the front porch of their home, while another picture shows Mrs. Fred Smith with her children. There is also a portrait of Hon. David L. Smith (1843-1912), a senator, banker, and merchant of West Cornwall.
      - Carl Stackman, N.D. (Box 26, Folder 23)
        Portrait of Rev. Carl Stackman. Stackman was the pastor at the Second Congregational Church of Cornwall from July 1902-August 1904.
      - Starr Family, circa 1895, N.D. (Box 26, Folder 24)
        Photographs of the Reverend Edward Comfort Starr and his family. Along with Rev. Starr, there are photos of Charles Comfort Starr, Edwin B. Starr, Mabel Emily Starr, and Fred Starr. Additionally, there are pictures of the Starr home and of the C.C. Starr "shanty" on Coltsfoot Mountain.
      - Harriet Soule, N.D. (Box 26, Folder 25)
        Photographs of eighteen-year-old Harriet Soule at the Scoville home before the Calhoun Ball.
      - William Stoddard, N.D. (Box 26, Folder 26)
        Portrait of William Stoddard, a "manufacturer at Golds Mills."
      - Joseph E. Struckus, N.D. (Box 26, Folder 27)
        Polaroid photo of Joseph E. Struckus.
      - Tankersley Family, N.D. (Box 26, Folder 28)
        Photographs of Bob Tankersley, Helen Sanford Tankersley, and Mrs. Sanford.
      - Mrs. Ticknor, N.D. (Box 26, Folder 29)
        Photograph of 100-year-old Mrs. Ticknor.
      - James Thurber, 1939-1954, N.D. (Box 26, Folder 30)
        Photographs of the cartoonist and author James Thurber. There are pictures of Thurber working at his typewriter and posing with a dog.
      - Pratt-Reuman Picnic, 1927 (Box 26, Folder 31)
        Photographs of a picnic held by the Pratt-Reuman familt at Cream Hill Lake.
      - Pratt-Reuman Picnics, 1935, N.D. (Box 26, Folder 32)
        Photographs of assorted family picnics held by the Pratt-Reuman family. One labeled photo depicts Lydia Griggs, Mabel Pratt, Ann Andrews, and M. Rogers.
      - Pratt-Reuman Family: Cream Hill Lake, circa 1900-1929, N.D. (Box 26, Folder 33)
        Photographs of the Pratt-Reuman family at Cream Hill Lake. There are photos of various family members, the original boat house, and Rocky Dell Cottage.
      - Porter Family, N.D. (Box 26, Folder 34)
        Portraits of Mr. and Mrs. Charles J. Porter.
      - Eric Richter, N.D. (Box 26, Folder 35)
        Photograph of Eric Richter.
      - Nathaniel Massey Urmston, N.D. (Box 27, Folder 1)
        Portrait of Reverend Nathaniel Massey Urmston.
      - George H. Vaill, N.D. (Box 27, Folder 2)
        Portrait of George H. Vaill.
      - Carl Van Doren, 1950, N.D. (Box 27, Folder 3)
        Photographs of Carl Van Doren (1885-1950). Van Doren was a Pulitzer Prize-winning author and critic who also taught at his alma mater, Columbia University.
      - Mark Van Doren Family, 1925-1958, N.D. (Box 27, Folder 4)
        Photographs of Pulitzer Prize-winner Mark Van Doren (1894-1972) and his family. Van Doren was an influential writer, poet, and professor at Columbia University. Many of the photos show Mark Van Doren at his home in Cornwall. There are also photos of Dorothy Van Doren, Charles Van Doren, and John Van Doren.
      - Wadsworth Family, N.D. (Box 27, Folder 5)
        Photographs of the Wadsworth family. There is a portrait of James Wadsworth, deacon of the North Cornwall Meeting House, and a picture of the grave of Samuel Wadsworth (1767-1817) in Canfield, Ohio.
      - Walker Family, N.D. (Box 27, Folder 6)
        Photographs of Cornwall physician Brad Walker and his wife Katie with their children.
        - Dr. W. B. Walker, N.D. (Box OS 2, Folder 20)
          Portrait of Dr. W. B. Walker.
      - Wedge Family, January 9, 1923, N.D. (Box 27, Folder 7)
        Photographs of the Wedge family of Cornwall Bridge. There are photos of Flora Wedge, Peter Wedge, Jr., and a family portrait showing Mark and Arthur Wedge with Mark's mother and daughter.
      - Charles Wetherby, N.D. (Box 27, Folder 8)
        Photograph of Reverend Charles Wetherby.
      - Wheaton Family, N.D. (Box 27, Folder 9)
        Photographs of attorney George Henry Wheaton and of his daughter Jessie Wheaton.
      - Mildred Whitcomb, N.D. (Box 27, Folder 10)
        Portrait of Mildred Whitcomb.
      - Edwin A. White Family, N.D. (Box 27, Folder 11)
        Photographs of Edwin A. White and his family
      - Ernest Whitney, N.D. (Box 27, Folder 12)
        Portrait of Ernest Whitney.
      - Susan Bate Williamson, N.D. (Box 27, Folder 13)
        Photograph of Susan Bate Williamson.
      - Yutzler Family, 1915-1943, N.D. (Box 27, Folder 14)
        Photographs of the Yutzler family. Multiple generations of Yutzlers operated a successful general store in West Cornwall. There a photos of Adam Yutzler, the first member of the family to settle in Cornwall, as well as many of his descendants, such as Frederick A. Yutzler, Harry Yutzler, Joseph Yutzler, Carl Yutzler, Frederick W. Yutzler, Blanch Yutzler, and "Dutch" Yutzler. There is also a photo of a painting by Arlington Yutzler and a group photograph sent to Florence Yutzler by her Sunday school class.
        Additionally, there are several photographs of the general store in West Cornwall showing customers like Huldah O'Donnell, Fred Scoville, and an unnamed member of the Gold family.
      - W. J. Wilcox, N.D. (Box 27, Folder 15)
        Portrait of W. J. Wilcox.
      - Miscellaneous, N.D. (Box 27, Folder 16)
        Unlabeled photographs of various Cornwall people. Many of the images are portraits, and one photo in particular depicts the "West Cornwall Base Ball Team."
        - Unidentified Couple, N.D. (Box OS 3, Folder 17)
          Photograph of an unidentified couple posed in front of their home.
        - Unidentified Family, N.D. (Box OS 3, Folder 19)
          Photograph of an unidentified family posing in front of their home.
      - Yale-Dean Wedding, 1912 (Box 27, Folder 24)
        Photograph from the wedding of Lucy Yale and Perry Dean in Cornwall Hollow. The photograph was donated by Margaret K. Wood.
      - Forest Woodman, N.D. (Box 27, Folder 25)
        Photograph of Forest Woodman.
      - Robert Hackins, N.D. (Box 34, Folder 4)
        Portrait of Robert Hackins.
      - Eva Hotchkiss, N.D. (Box 34, Folder 5)
        Portrait of Eva Hotchkiss at age two.
      - C. E. Graves, N.D. (Box 34, Folder 6)
        Portrait of C. E. Graves of Falls Village, Conn.
      - Arthur Gibbs, N.D. (Box 34, Folder 7)
        Portrait of Arthur Gibbs.
      - Butler Family, N.D. (Box 34, Folder 8)
        Photographs of Willie W. Butler and Mag Butler.
      - Mrs. George Babcock, N.D. (Box 34, Folder 9)
        Portrait of Mrs. George Babcock.
      - Mattie Kimberly, N.D. (Box 34, Folder 10)
        Portrait of Mattie Kimberly of North Colebrook, Conn.
      - Hanna Family, N.D. (Box 34, Folder 11)
        Portraits of Mr. and Mrs. Hanna.
      - Morris Family, N.D. (Box 34, Folder 12)
        Portraits of Hattie and Libbie Morris.
      - Ida Phillips, N.D. (Box 34, Folder 13)
        Portrait of Ida Phillips.
      - Ethel and Percy Bartelle (Box 34, Folder 14)
        Portrait of Ethel and Percy Bartelle as children.
      - William Dakin, N.D. (Box 34, Folder 15)
        Portrait of William Dakin.
      - Mrs. M. Brinton, N.D. (Box 34, Folder 16)
        Portrait of Mrs. M. Brinton.
      - Olive Rogers, N.D. (Box 34, Folder 17)
        Portrait of music teacher Olive Rogers.
      - Unlabeled Large Portraits, N.D. (Box 34, Folder 18)
        Large unlabeled portraits.
      - Unlabeled Small Portraits, N.D. (Box 34, Folder 19)
        Unlabeled small portraits.
      - Ernest D. Clark Vacation Photos, circa 1908 (Box 35, Folder 11)
        Photographs from a trip that Ernest D. Clark took to North Carolina.
      - Marian Blake, 1953, N.D. (Box 35, Folder 12)
        Photographs of Marian Blake and her home in Torrington, Conn.
      - Jack Kling, N.D. (Box 35, Folder 13)
        Photograph of Jack Kling in his military uniform.
      - Helen Trowbridge House, N.D. (Box 35, Folder 14)
        Photograph of the home owned by Helen Trowbrdige.
      - Henry Seidel Canby, N.D. (Box 35, Folder 15)
        Portrait of H. S. Canby.
      - Mark Van Doren, February 1963 (Box 35, Folder 16)
        Photograph of Mark Van Doren.
      - George Clark Musket and Powder Horn (Box 35, Folder 34)
        Photographs of the Revolutionary War musket and powder horn owned by Ensign George Clark.
      - Jennifer deSimas, March 16, 1992 (Box 35, Folder 35)
        Photograph of Cornwall Historical Society curator Jennifer de Simas with a quilt.
      - Sam Waterston, N.D. (Box 35, Folder 36)
        Photograph of Sam Waterston delivering a Memorial Day address.
      - Minnie Sturges Bungalow, N.D. (Box 35, Folder 44)
        Photograph of the bungalow owned by Minnie Sturges.
      - Peg and Laura Woolsey (Box 35, Folder 45)
        Portrait of Peg and Laura Woolsey as children.
      - W. G. Fennell, N.D. (Box OS 2, Folder 18)
        Portrait of Rev. W.G. Fennell, pastor of the East Cornwall Baptist Church.
      - Bachrach Portrait of Unknown Woman, N.D. (Box OS 2, Folder 19)
        Portrait of an unknown woman by Bachrach Photography.
      - Fritz Burehl, N.D. (Box OS 3, Folder 3)
        Photograph of Fritz Burehl.
      - England Family (Box OS 4, Object 4)
        Photograph of the England family posed in front of their home.
    - Topics
      - Schools
        - Adelphic Institute, N.D. (Box 27, Folder 17)
          Photographs of the Adelphic Institute building on Town Street in North Cornwall.
        - Cream Hill Agricultural School, 1976-1989, N.D. (Box 27, Folder 18)
          Photographs of the Cream Hill Agricultural School. The school, which was the first such institution in the United States, was located on the Gold family farm in North Cornwall and operated from 1845-1869. Today, the structure is under the care of the Connecticut Antique Machinery Association and is located in Kent, Conn. There is also a group photograph of students and teachers from 1859-1860.
        - Housatonic Valley Institute, 1890, N.D. (Box 27, Folder 19)
          Photographs of the Housatonic Valley Institute. There are photographs of the buildings and grounds, as well as various students and the school's football team.
        - Marvelwood School, 1961-1995, N.D. (Box 27, Folder 20)
          Photographs of the Marvelwood School in Cornwall Plain. There are photos of the administration building, which was located in a home formerly owned by the Cochrane family, and of the Trustee House, which was located in a home once owned by Whiting Wilcox.
        - Rumsey Hall School, 1927, N.D. (Box 27, Folder 21)
          Photographs of the Rumsey Hall School in Cornwall Plain. There are photos of the exteriors and interiors of buildings associated with the school.
        - Rumsey Hall School: Part II, circa 1920-1927 (Box 27, Folder 22)
          Additional photographs of buildings used by the Rumsey Hall School, including a group of children posed in front of the boarding house.
        - Rumsey Hall Students, 1918, N.D. (Box 27, Folder 23)
          Photographs of Rumsey Hall Students. There are class photos, as well as a picture of the football team. Many of the photographs were taken by H.D. Hine of New Milford, Conn.
        - Housatonic Valley Regional High School, 1946, N.D. (Box 28, Folder 1)
          Photographs of Housatonic Valley Regional High School.
        - Cornwall Consolidated School, 1939-January 1995, N.D. (Box 28, Folder 2)
          Photographs of the Cornwall Consolidated School on Cream Hill Road. The building was designed by T. Merrill Prentice and built from 1939-1940. There are photos of the building's exterior and interior, as well as pictures documenting its construction.
        - Cornwall Consolidated School: Students and Teachers, 1941-1968, N.D. (Box 28, Folder 3)
          Photographs of students and teachers at the Cornwall Consolidated School. Many of the pictures are class photos.
        - Hunstville School, 1900 (Box 28, Box 4)
          Class photograph from the Huntsville School.
        - District 1 School House, 1933-1976, N.D. (Box 28, Folder 5)
          Photographs of the District 1 School House in Cornwall Bridge. The structure was built in 1909 to replace an earlier school and was later converted into the home of the Cavanaugh family.
        - District 1: Teachers and Students, 1894-1938, N.D. (Box 28, Folder 6)
          Photographs of students and teachers from District 1. Many of the photos are class pictures and include local teacher Mabel Engisch.
        - District 2 School, 1903-1918, N.D. (Box 28, Folder 7)
          Photographs from the second school district located in Cornwall Plain. There are photos of the interior and exterior of the school house, as well as several class pictures.
          - District 2 School and Students (Box OS 3, Folder 14)
            Photograph of students posed outside the District 2 School.
        - District 3 School, June 18, 1911-July 1917, N.D. (Box 28, Folder 8)